Guide to Variety's Protected Material Department Submissions
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Submissions, 1916-1925; 7.0; (14 boxes)
  - Sans, Pearl, 1917 September 22 (Box 12, Folder 402)
  - Savage, Howard, and Helen Savage, 1917 October 31 (Box 12, Folder 403)
  - Schooler, Dave, and Ed Rose, 1917 November 30 (Box 12, Folder 404)
  - Scott, Bert, and Shep Walde, 1922 July 18 (Box 12, Folder 405)
  - Schubach, Albert, 1918 December 21 (Box 12, Folder 406)
  - Seato, A., 1917 September 12 (Box 12, Folder 407)
  - Seymour, A. E., 1923 April 7 (Box 12, Folder 408)
  - Seymour, Blanche, 1918 December 3 (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Shannon, Frank L., 1918 March 18 (Box 12, Folder 410)
  - Shannon, James R., 1918 April 23 (Box 12, Folder 411)
  - Shaw, Leila, and Fred J. Beaman, 1918 September 8 (Box 12, Folder 412)
  - Small, Billy, 1917 October 2 (Box 12, Folder 413)
  - Sparks, Alec, 1916 September 11 (Box 12, Folder 414)
  - Spencer, Lloyd, 1918 July 12 (Box 12, Folder 415)
  - Stauton, Leon, 1919 March 20 (Box 12, Folder 416)
  - Sterling, Karl, and Bertha Sterling, 1919 March 4 (Box 12, Folder 417)
  - Sterling Rose Trio, 1917 September 12 (Box 12, Folder 418)
  - Sternard, Billy, 1925 February 16 (Box 12, Folder 419)
  - Stewart, George, 1918 July 13 (Box 12, Folder 420)
  - Strewel, Henry B., 1918 June 23 (Box 12, Folder 421)
  - Tenley, Elmer, 1916 December 5 (Box 12, Folder 422)
  - Tenney, Alan Spencer, 1918 January 25 (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - Totten, Joseph Byron, 1918 July 15 (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Treynor, Blair, 1917 January 17; 1917 February 1 (Box 12, Folder 425-426)
  - Turelly, Arthur Stern, 1918 January 19 (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Valentine, Robert, 1922 December 6 (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Van and Schenck, 1918 December 22 (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Van, Thomas S., undated (Box 12, Folder 430)
  - Vann and Vernon, 1924 February 6 (Box 12, Folder 431)
  - Vernon, Hope, 1922 September 21 (Box 12, Folder 432)
  - Virden, Lewis, 1917 September 3 (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Wallace, Frederick, 1917 January 20–1918 January 25 (Box 13, Folder 434-436)
  - Wanzer, Arthur G. and Palmer, 1918 March 18 (Box 13, Folder 437)
  - Warwick, Henry, 1917 September 29 (Box 13, Folder 438)
  - Warwick, Henry, and Lewis B. Foley, 1917 September 19; 1917 October 5 (Box 13, Folder 439-440)
  - Wayne and Marshall, 1916 June 20 (Box 13, Folder 441)
  - Weber, Al F., undated (Box 13, Folder 442)
  - Westover, Clyde, 1921 November 21 (Box 13, Folder 443)
  - Wheeler, Bert, 1916 November 15; 1919 July 15 (Box 13, Folder 444-445)
  - White, Billy, and Ada White
    - 1916 August 23 (Box 13, Folder 446)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 14 (Oversize), Folder 475-476)
  - White, Elise, 1917 August 8 (Box 13, Folder 447)
  - White, Kirk, and Dick Massie, 1922 November 20 (Box 13, Folder 448)
  - White, Oliver, undated (Box 13, Folder 449)
  - Whittle, A. G., 1917 January 15 (Box 13, Folder 450)
  - Williams, Jack, and Cora Williams, 1917 August 30 (Box 13, Folder 451)
  - Willis, Roy Jay, 1917 September 28 (Box 13, Folder 452)
  - Wilson and Aubrey, 1916 February 20; 1919 March 29 (Box 13, Folder 453-454)
  - Wilson, Vera, 1925 January 30 (Box 13, Folder 455)
  - Wohlman, Al, 1923 January 12 (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - Wolf, E. W., 1916 November 27 (Box 13, Folder 457)
  - Woolsey, Bobby, 1917 November 24; 1919 May 7 (Box 13, Folder 458-459)
  - Zoeller, Edward, 1916 February 25 (Box 13, Folder 460)
  - Unidentified, 1917 September 12; undated (Box 13, Folder 461-464)
    Includes envelopes
- Restricted Fragile, 1916-1925; 1.04; (3 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, Folder 2 (Box 15, Folder 477)
  - Box 1, Folder 3 (Box 15, Folder 478)
  - Box 1, Folder 5 (Box 15, Folder 479)
  - Box 1, Folder 8 (Box 15, Folder 480)
  - Box 1, Folder 9 (Box 15, Folder 481)
  - Box 1, Folder 11 (Box 15, Folder 482)
  - Box 1, Folder 16 (Box 15, Folder 483)
  - Box 1, Folder 18 (Box 15, Folder 484)
  - Box 1, Folder 19 (Box 15, Folder 485)
  - Box 2, Folder 25 (Box 15, Folder 486)
  - Box 2, Folder 27 (Box 15, Folder 487)
  - Box 2, Folder 30 (Box 15, Folder 488)
  - Box 2, Folder 32 (Box 15, Folder 489)
  - Box 2, Folder 34 (Box 15, Folder 490)
  - Box 2, Folder 40 (Box 15, Folder 491)
  - Box 2, Folder 46 (Box 15, Folder 492)
  - Box 3, Folder 51 (Box 15, Folder 493)
  - Box 3, Folder 52 (Box 15, Folder 494)
  - Box 3, Folder 53 (Box 15, Folder 495)
  - Box 3, Folder 54 (Box 15, Folder 496)
  - Box 3, Folder 55 (Box 15, Folder 497)
  - Box 3, Folder 56 (Box 15, Folder 498)
  - Box 3, Folder 57 (Box 15, Folder 499)
  - Box 3, Folder 58 (Box 15, Folder 500)
  - Box 3, Folder 59 (Box 15, Folder 501)
  - Box 3, Folder 60 (Box 15, Folder 502)
  - Box 3, Folder 61 (Box 15, Folder 503)
  - Box 3, Folder 62 (Box 15, Folder 504)
  - Box 3, Folder 63 (Box 15, Folder 505)
  - Box 3, Folder 64 (Box 15, Folder 506)
  - Box 3, Folder 69 (Box 15, Folder 507)
  - Box 3, Folder 71 (Box 15, Folder 508)
  - Box 3, Folder 72 (Box 15, Folder 509)
  - Box 3, Folder 73 (Box 15, Folder 510)
  - Box 3, Folder 74 (Box 15, Folder 511)
  - Box 3, Folder 75 (Box 15, Folder 512)
  - Box 4, Folder 76 (Box 15, Folder 513)
  - Box 4, Folder 80 (Box 15, Folder 514)
  - Box 4, Folder 83 (Box 15, Folder 515)
  - Box 4, Folder 89 (Box 15, Folder 516)
  - Box 4, Folder 92 (Box 15, Folder 517)
  - Box 4, Folder 94 (Box 15, Folder 518)
  - Box 4, Folder 96 (Box 15, Folder 519)
  - Box 4, Folder 99 (Box 15, Folder 520)
  - Box 4, Folder 105 (Box 15, Folder 521)
  - Box 5, Folder 116 (Box 15, Folder 522)
  - Box 5, Folder 119 (Box 15, Folder 523)
  - Box 5, Folder 120 (Box 15, Folder 524)
  - Box 5, Folder 121 (Box 15, Folder 525)
  - Box 5, Folder 123 (Box 15, Folder 526)
  - Box 5, Folder 125 (Box 15, Folder 527)
  - Box 5, Folder 131 (Box 15, Folder 528)
  - Box 5, Folder 136 (Box 15, Folder 529)
  - Box 5, Folder 145 (Box 15, Folder 530)
  - Box 5, Folder 147 (Box 15, Folder 531)
  - Box 6, Folder 148 (Box 15, Folder 532)
  - Box 6, Folder 149 (Box 15, Folder 533)
  - Box 6, Folder 150 (Box 15, Folder 534)
  - Box 6, Folder 152 (Box 15, Folder 535)
  - Box 6, Folder 153 (Box 15, Folder 536)
  - Box 6, Folder 156 (Box 15, Folder 537)
  - Box 6, Folder 158 (Box 15, Folder 538)
  - Box 6, Folder 163 (Box 15, Folder 539)
  - Box 6, Folder 165 (Box 15, Folder 540)
  - Box 6, Folder 170 (Box 15, Folder 541)
  - Box 6, Folder 174 (Box 15, Folder 542)
  - Box 7, Folder 117 (Box 16, Folder 543)
  - Box 7, Folder 179 (Box 16, Folder 544)
  - Box 7, Folder 180 (Box 16, Folder 545)
  - Box 7, Folder 181 (Box 16, Folder 546)
  - Box 7, Folder 183 (Box 16, Folder 547)
  - Box 7, Folder 186 (Box 16, Folder 548)
  - Box 7, Folder 187 (Box 16, Folder 549)
  - Box 7, Folder 189 (Box 16, Folder 550)
  - Box 7, Folder 194 (Box 16, Folder 551)
  - Box 7, Folder 195 (Box 16, Folder 552)
  - Box 7, Folder 196 (Box 16, Folder 553)
  - Box 7, Folder 198 (Box 16, Folder 554)
  - Box 7, Folder 201 (Box 16, Folder 555)
  - Box 8, Folder 208 (Box 16, Folder 556)
  - Box 8, Folder 211 (Box 16, Folder 557)
  - Box 8, Folder 213 (Box 16, Folder 558)
  - Box 8, Folder 214 (Box 16, Folder 559)
  - Box 8, Folder 222 (Box 16, Folder 560)
  - Box 8, Folder 228 (Box 16, Folder 561)
  - Box 8, Folder 233 (Box 16, Folder 562)
  - Box 8, Folder 237 (Box 16, Folder 563)
  - Box 8, Folder 238 (Box 16, Folder 564)
  - Box 8, Folder 239 (Box 16, Folder 565)
  - Box 8, Folder 240 (Box 16, Folder 566)
  - Box 8, Folder 241 (Box 16, Folder 567)
  - Box 8, Folder 243 (Box 16, Folder 568)
  - Box 8, Folder 253 (Box 16, Folder 569)
  - Box 8, Folder 256 (Box 16, Folder 570)
  - Box 8, Folder 258 (Box 16, Folder 571)
  - Box 8, Folder 260 (Box 16, Folder 572)
  - Box 8, Folder 261 (Box 16, Folder 573)
  - Box 8, Folder 262 (Box 16, Folder 574)
  - Box 9, Folder 263 (Box 16, Folder 575)
  - Box 9, Folder 264 (Box 16, Folder 576)
  - Box 9, Folder 265 (Box 16, Folder 577)
  - Box 9, Folder 266 (Box 16, Folder 578)
  - Box 9, Folder 267 (Box 16, Folder 579)
  - Box 9, Folder 269 (Box 16, Folder 580)
  - Box 9, Folder 271 (Box 16, Folder 581)
  - Box 9, Folder 275 (Box 16, Folder 582)
  - Box 9, Folder 277 (Box 16, Folder 583)
  - Box 9, Folder 278 (Box 16, Folder 584)
  - Box 9, Folder 279 (Box 16, Folder 585)
  - Box 9, Folder 280 (Box 16, Folder 586)
  - Box 9, Folder 281 (Box 16, Folder 587)
  - Box 9, Folder 282 (Box 16, Folder 588)
  - Box 9, Folder 287 (Box 16, Folder 589)
  - Box 9, Folder 292 (Box 16, Folder 590)
  - Box 9, Folder 294 (Box 16, Folder 591)
  - Box 9, Folder 296 (Box 16, Folder 592)
  - Box 9, Folder 303 (Box 16, Folder 593)
  - Box 9, Folder 304 (Box 16, Folder 594)
  - Box 10, Folder 305 (Box 16, Folder 595)
  - Box 10, Folder 307 (Box 16, Folder 596)
  - Box 10, Folder 308 (Box 16, Folder 597)
  - Box 10, Folder 312 (Box 16, Folder 598)
  - Box 10, Folder 313 (Box 16, Folder 599)
  - Box 10, Folder 316 (Box 16, Folder 600)
  - Box 10, Folder 319 (Box 16, Folder 601)
  - Box 10, Folder 320 (Box 16, Folder 602)
  - Box 10, Folder 323 (Box 16, Folder 603)
  - Box 10, Folder 324 (Box 16, Folder 604)
  - Box 10, Folder 329 (Box 16, Folder 605)
  - Box 10, Folder 337 (Box 16, Folder 606)
  - Box 10, Folder 339 (Box 16, Folder 607)
  - Box 10, Folder 340 (Box 16, Folder 608)
  - Box 10, Folder 341 (Box 16, Folder 609)
  - Box 10, Folder 345 (Box 16, Folder 610)
  - Box 10, Folder 346 (Box 16, Folder 611)
  - Box 10, Folder 351 (Box 16, Folder 612)
  - Box 10, Folder 352 (Box 16, Folder 613)
  - Box 11, Folder 356 (Box 17, Folder 614)
  - Box 11, Folder 358 (Box 17, Folder 615)
  - Box 11, Folder 359 (Box 17, Folder 616)
  - Box 11, Folder 367 (Box 17, Folder 617)
  - Box 11, Folder 368 (Box 17, Folder 618)
  - Box 11, Folder 369 (Box 17, Folder 619)
  - Box 11, Folder 370 (Box 17, Folder 620)
  - Box 11, Folder 374 (Box 17, Folder 621)
  - Box 11, Folder 376 (Box 17, Folder 622)
  - Box 11, Folder 378 (Box 17, Folder 623)
  - Box 11, Folder 381 (Box 17, Folder 624)
  - Box 11, Folder 385 (Box 17, Folder 625)
  - Box 11, Folder 387 (Box 17, Folder 626)
  - Box 11, Folder 390 (Box 17, Folder 627)
  - Box 12, Folder 392 (Box 17, Folder 628)
  - Box 12, Folder 393 (Box 17, Folder 629)
  - Box 12, Folder 394 (Box 17, Folder 630)
  - Box 12, Folder 398 (Box 17, Folder 631)
  - Box 12, Folder 406 (Box 17, Folder 632)
  - Box 12, Folder 412 (Box 17, Folder 633)
  - Box 12, Folder 414 (Box 17, Folder 634)
  - Box 12, Folder 415 (Box 17, Folder 635)
  - Box 12, Folder 420 (Box 17, Folder 636)
  - Box 12, Folder 422 (Box 17, Folder 637)
  - Box 12, Folder 426 (Box 17, Folder 638)
  - Box 13, Folder 435 (Box 17, Folder 639)
  - Box 13, Folder 442 (Box 17, Folder 640)
  - Box 13, Folder 445 (Box 17, Folder 641)
  - Box 13, Folder 447 (Box 17, Folder 642)
  - Box 13, Folder 450 (Box 17, Folder 643)
  - Box 13, Folder 451 (Box 17, Folder 644)
  - Box 13, Folder 454 (Box 17, Folder 645)
  - Box 13, Folder 462 (Box 17, Folder 646)
  - Box 13, Folder 464 (Box 17, Folder 647)
  - Box 14 (Oversize), Folder 470 (Box 17, Folder 648)
  - Box 14 (Oversize), Folder 471 (Box 17, Folder 649)